ultramercial.com 2014-12-01

# Ultramercial, the audience engagement engine

Ultramercial Privacy Policy

Ultramercial makes every attempt to respect and protect the privacy of the individuals that use our services. 

The intent of this document is to inform you what we collect and how we use it.

**Types of Information**

We obtain two kinds of information: the kind that your Web Browser supplies automatically to every Web site that you visit (such as your computer’s Internet address) and the kind that you provide explicitly (such as if you type your name or email address into one of our Web pages). 

We require, collect and store the automatically-supplied information and use it in aggregate for a variety of purposes related to delivering the Commercial and the ensuing reward. 

Whenever we ask for personal information, we will tell you what it is for and who will receive it. We will do our best to make sure that nobody else does, except in aggregate form (such as what percentage of people provided the information.) 

**Browser identification**

Ultramercial sets cookies on your computer every time you load one of our pages. This allows us to uniquely identify your browser and therefore track which pages and advertisers you have visited through the ultramercial.com domain. We cannot read cookies set by other Web sites, and they cannot read the ones that we set. 

Cookies allow us to recognize you when you return to our site, and we use this information for certain purposes such as choosing the advertising campaign to deliver, and passing you through to the content that you requested. You must accept and store our cookies in order to successfully complete an Ultramercial. 

In addition, Ultramercial automatically collects information that your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to troubleshoot our services and occasionally analyze it in summary form in order to provide statistics about our visitors. 

We store the page that you initially requested on the destination site and the page that you requested it from. This is necessary so that we can send you to that page at the end of your session with us, and provide aggregate information to the publisher about page popularity and use of the Ultramercial.   
**  
Separation of Information**

While we collect a significant amount of information about your configuration and viewing habits, we have no idea who you are. All of the information is abstracted through a randomly generated identifier that is stored in the cookie on your computer.

Nobody on your computer can see any of the information that we collect about you, and we cannot see any of the information on your computer that we did not set. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

Ultramercial occasionally needs to tie personally identifying information to your browser. One case in which we do this is when you take advantage of the ‘free pass’ we sometimes grant directly to you after you email us with problems accessing the site. We store such information in order to troubleshoot and resolve your issue, and never use that information for any other purpose or share that information with anybody outside Ultramercial. Neither advertisers nor publishers are able to access that information.

**Direct Response Information**

Occasionally, advertisers may request personally identifying information from you as part of a campaign. Providing this information is always optional and clearly marked as such. Information that you provide this way is provided exclusively to the underlying advertiser and is subject to their privacy policy. 

Each advertiser that wishes to have this information must request it themselves. 

**Sharing of Information**

We may share personally identifiable information that you supply – such as your email address or telephone number – in any of the following limited circumstances:   
\- We have your consent.   
\- We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.   
\- We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Ultramercial, its users or the public. 

We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which Ultramercial LLC or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country. 

In the event of a transfer of ownership of Ultramercial LLC, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, it is possible that personally identifying information may be transferred and become subject to a different privacy policy. Such action becomes subject to Changes to this Policy as described below. 

We routinely share aggregated information with others, including detailed non-personal information with the publishers and advertisers underwriting the campaign. This information is only available in aggregate form. 

**Links**

Our advertisers may present links as part of their campaigns that deliver services that are developed by people over whom Ultramercial exercises no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information. Please refer to their privacy policy concerning these issues.

**Changes to this Policy**

Please note this Privacy Policy will by necessity change from time to time and we will maintain this page as the current version of the privacy policy. 

**Automatic opt-out**

It is an unfortunate possibility that that information collected under a prior version of this privacy policy may be handled under terms of a new privacy policy. In such circumstances where personally identifiable information (like your email address) would be used in terms inconsistent with the policy in force at the time the information was collected, we will assume that you do not wish to have your information transferred and destroy it as we are able. 

If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time. Our most recent contact information is available at the web page <http://www.ultramercial.com/#contact>
